him for a slew of charges. I got U.N. handcuffed and Joey, the cougar's amp I go back to the
backyard patio to try amp to process wtf just happened. Next day we wake up to spray tan wife
knocking on homeowner cougar's front door. She begs Joey amp I to drop the charges on her husband
bc he already has felonies and he will go to jail forever blah blah blah. I called her a lot of
choice words since in my head this was her fault to begin with. That's when she said she would pay
to fix my car, it was undrivable in current state. After consulting Joey we agreed if she would get
it fixed on Monday. This went down Saturday night, it was Sunday morning now. She agreed to pay it.
Monday we got a ride in red bmw to the Austin Texas district attorney's office. Meet w ask da
amp explain we want to drop charges. We sign amp get notarized a paper saying we dropped charges
and ada tells us that even though we are saying we don't want to press charges the city of Austin
still can charge him. A detail we forgot to mention to spray tan wife. Joey amp I then drive
my vehicle with broken glass covering the interior of my car amp my head out the driver's window to
see the road bc windshield was spider webbed. We go to a really small family-owned auto glass shop
that was in the woods as it is the closest one to mansion neighborhood. The guys are laughing as
they look at the car you boys pissed somebody off real bad. We were there a total of hours waiting
on them to replace all the windows and front back windshield and in this time we told the story of
Saturday night. The owner was really cool and actually gave us beer to drink while we waited
which I didn't understand but loved. So Joey amp I had the idea to make some money from this venture.
We asked said owner if he wanted to make some money as well he was game. So the repairs cost
we told him we'd give him almost all the money we had at the time if he created a bill saying it
cost for the repairs. He happily did it for us. Next day we met tanning salon wife and husband he
had posted bail at their bank. Joey stayed in the car bc he didn't want to get killed by husband.
I was sitting in lobby with the notarized we are dropping charges paperwork and the bill for all
new windows. They get there I give her the bill praying they hadn't priced out all new windows
on a car recently. She gets in line without saying a word amp get Chris Benjamins. I then give her
the notarized paper amp she gives me in a very drug deal Sopranos-esque over under transaction.
We then drove straight to Shreveport Louisiana without to go to the Horseshoe Casino that was
our experience in Austin Texas. If y'all got any questions let me know I have pics of my car from
the morning after but they're in my email from amp I'm having a hard time finding them. You'll post
them in comments when I find them. Hope y'all enjoyed and yes every single word of that story
is factual.